Going to EDC Las Vegas for the first time? Here
are brand-new tips to help you have the
best possible experience at EDC in 2025.
What’s up rave fam, I’m Joe, your
Rave Tour Guide! I help ravers like
you get the most out of their EDC
experience. If you’re new here,
consider subscribing for more EDC
content! And if you want even more tips,
check out my previous first-timer guides. I’ll
leave the links in the description box below.
Tip 1: Trade Kandi with Other Headliners
Kandi trading is an amazing way to connect with
your fellow headliners. Don’t be afraid to ask
someone if they want to trade—whether you’re at a
stage, resting at a table, or walking throughout
the festival. I believe some of the best moments
happen when you share a bracelet that represents
your new connection. Like a piece of kandi with a
special word or phrase that captures the moment.
Tip 2: Use a Totem for Easy Navigation
If you’re in a group, a totem is a must. It makes
it way easier to find your
crew and move through crowds.
Tip 3: Catch a Surprise Set
Some of the best sets at EDC
aren’t even announced! Last year,
we caught Fred again’s first-ever EDC set
— it was my favorite set of the entire
weekend! This year, there’s rumors of an
ISOKNOCK set, possibly at circuitGROUNDS!
Tip 4: Check Out Activation Experiences
Big brands bring out freebies, unique drinks,
and pop-up stages—like Dunkin’ last
year! If they bring back Dunkin’ again,
it’s definitely worth checking out.
Tip 5: Explore Downtown EDC
Beyond the main stages, places like the
YeeDC Country Saloon offer their own vibe,
bar, and lineup. And, if there’s a line at the
experience you want to do, don’t hesitate—it’s
worth it. Last year I didn’t do the Kandi
Casino because I thought the lines were long,
only to find out they took 15-20 minutes. If I
would have known, we would've definitely waited.
Are you finding value in these tips so far? If so,
please hit that like button to help spread
the video to more ravers on YouTube and
consider subscribing to the Rave Tour
Guide channel for more EDC content.
We have five more, really good first-timer
tips, so be sure to stick around until the end!
Tip 6: Make EDC Your Power-Up!
EDC isn’t just a festival—it’s a launchpad for
your next level. Before you go, take a moment
to recognize how far you’ve come. After EDC,
don’t let that energy fade—channel it into your
life and goals. The most successful people don’t
just experience transformation—they plan for it.
Let’s map out your next moves together—book
a free Rave Life Strategy Session now! The
link is in the description—take action today
and make this your most powerful year yet!
Tip 7: Watch Intermissions at kineticFIELD
EDC’s biggest stage has insane production—and
you can see it all in action during
intermissions and the closing show.
Tip 8: Stay Until the End (At Least One Night!)
Day 2 is the best day to stay
‘til the end—the vibes are unreal,
and kineticFIELD’s closing show is
the perfect way to end the night.
There you have it folks, my 8 BRAND NEW
first-timer tips for EDC Las Vegas 2025. If you
found this video helpful hit that like button!
And if you want even more first-timer tips,
check out my past videos for you to select
right here. See you under the electric sky! 🌟